It takes an awful lot to kill a person.
Hunting Season is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Raja Collins.
When a reclusive survivalist and his daughter rescue a mysterious, wounded woman from a river, they become
entangled in a deadly web of violence and revenge, forcing them to confront a brutal criminal to survive.
Bowdrie, played by Mel Gibson.
January, played by Shelley Hennig.
Alejandro, played by Jordi Mollà.
Tag, played by Sofia Hublitz.
Davenport, played by A.J. Buckley.
Sheriff Brake, played by James DuMont.
Hunting Season is a 2025 American action crime drama film written by Adam
Hampton, directed by RJ Collins and starring Mel Gibson.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.